

# Arman Ajabkhani

SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER - BACK END

#### **PROFILE**

A software engineer with more than 9 years experience in software developing with Several roles including developer, designer, team lead in various projects.

Communicative, high interaction with team-mates, responsibility and perseverance.

Intrested in learning new concepts, technical/nontechnical challanges ,distributed systems, also improving the Software Quality(functional or non-functional).

#### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Science** from Sheikh Bahaee Isfahan University in Software Engineering from September 2000 to September 2006.

#### LANGUAGES

English(intermediate)

Persian(native)

Germany(elementary)

# **CONTACT**

Email: arm.khani@gmail.com Mobile: +98 912 8589 456

LinkedIn: Arman Ajabkhani's profile

Github: Arman's profile

Resume Suorce: LaTeX graphical resume

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Snapp

## Senior Java Developer

July 2019 - Present

Snapp's main product is a smart transportation system(like Uber).

Senior java developer in Fintech team:

- Designing and implementing new generation Financial management services for users and drivers.
- Providing services for more than 2 million users.
- Developing services with SpringBoot, Spring Cloud, MySql, OpenShift and Redis.
- Responsible for designing and development of Payment and Wallet Management Services.

#### Sava Arman Kish

## Senior Java Developer

Nov 2018 - Jul 2019

Sava Arman Kish is a crypto-currencies Exchange start-up.

Senior java developer in the Exchange back-end team:

- Developing reactive services using RxJava and Vert.x and Swagger.
- Responsible for designing, development and maintaining CRM and notification services.
- Designing and implementing features and fixing bugs in several micro-services.

### **TOSAN**

## Senior Java Developer /Team Lead

Nov 2011 -Nov 2018

Tosan provide Payment ,Financial and Banking solution.

Team lead in Channel Manager team:

- Mentoring, coaching, training and planning tasks for the team members.
- Analysis, Design, Development, Deployment & Maintenance several applications & micro-services.
- Designing and developing some complicated features in open banking API.

Java developer in Channel Manager Team:

- Developing functionalities for tracking and authentication and authorization.
- Developing and maintaining Exchange and Corporate Banking subsystems.
- Providing serveral financial and payment services for front-end teams.
- Developing and implementing RMI and Web Services (REST / SOAP JAX-WS).
- Implementing several library using Spring/JPA/Hibernate for othen teams

# Elm o Sanat

# C#/ASP.NET Developer

Sep 2010 -Oct 2011

C#/ASP.NET developer in School product Team:

- Implementing several new features and maintain in the School application.
- Implementing features in a custom report generator.
- Implementing virtual replication on SQL Server with use web service.



# Arman Ajabkhani SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER - BACK END

# PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Spring
Spring Boot
Spring MVC
Spring Security
Spring Cloud
Spring Batch
Spring Data / JPA/ Hibernate
Spring AOP / aspectj
Vert.x / RxJava
Redis / Redisson
Oracle
MySQL / SQL Server
Gradle / Maven
Swagger UI/ Codegen
Git / Subversion / TFS
ActiveMQ/ Rabbit MQ
Apache Tomcat
OAuth / JWT
JUnit / TestNg / Mockito
C#
LATEX .